<Document>
  # 8: At least make a minimum effort to have your name fit realistically.

Excessively OOC names are disallowed, and are defined as names which are:
- 8.1.1e: Intentionally hard to read/spell.
- 8.1.2e: References to in-game mechanics or OOC terminology.
- 8.1.3e: Historical or famous people/media.
- 8.1.4e: Names of other in-game characters.
- 8.1.5e: Any form of nonsensical or low-effort name.

Names should not contain titles/honorifics, and must follow all other rules (no slurs/sexual names/etc)

Clowns and mimes are exempt from the prohibition on titles/honorifics, and have loosened restrictions on low effort and implausible names.

  ## Species naming conventions.
Species have naming conventions that are part of their in-universe culture.
These may be subverted if they have a sufficient amount of in-character reasoning and effort explaining their
non-standard name. Non-standard names are held to higher scrutiny and you may be questioned on why your name
breaks these conventions.

List:

8.2.1: Humans typically use the Firstname Lastname convention.

Allowed:
- Tom Fisher
- Spacey Chapman

Disallowed:
- Dr. Tom Fisher
- Walter White
- George Washington
- Joe Biden
- Ben Dover
- Mike Hunt

8.2.2: Dwarfs typically use the human convention in a viking theme.

Allowed:
- Ingrid Firebreath
- Erik Lightningclaw

Disallowed:
- Thor Ragnarok

8.2.3: Lizards typically use either their own, unique naming style (see examples), or the Verb-article-Noun convention.

Allowed:
- Saak-Bur
- Gai-Meesei
- Azbai-Jeen
- Cleans-the-Airlocks

Disallowed:
- Bans-the-Admins

8.2.4: Slimes typically use the same naming conventions as humans, or have names that are onomonopia with an optional last name.

Allowed:
- Foolp Suub
- Foolp

Disallowed:
- Slime

8.2.5: Diona typically have calm, nature themed, Noun of Noun style names.

Allowed:
- Petal of Tranquility
- Garden of Relaxation

Disallowed:
- Tree but Alive

8.2.6: Mothmen typically use moth-themed latin sounding names, or light themed names.

Allowed:
- Socrates Temnora
- Sierra Lightseeker
- James Nightflitter
- Blee Sparkle
- Iris Blimm
- Flip Flop

Disallowed:
- Fucking Moth

8.2.7: Arachnids typically use spider-themed latin sounding names.

Allowed:
- Argyroneta Reticulatus
- Loxosceles Domesticus

Disallowed:
- Spider-Man

8.2.8: Vox typically use a single name made of random syllables, often with repeating patterns. Names should not be excessively long or be so repetitive/convoluted as to be unreadable.

Allowed:
- Hirixashahre
- Xapikrikrik

Disallowed:
- Chipikirchitchitchitbecretretrer
- Trololol

</Document>